Hero
英雄
歌手：Mariah Carey
压制:随Feng
There's a hero
有一位英雄
If you look inside your heart
如果你寻觅内心深处
You don't have to be afraid
你无需恐惧害怕
Of what you are
自己如何
There's an answer
有一个答案
If you reach into your soul
如果你深入自己的灵魂
And the sorrow that you know
你会了解个中的悲伤
Will melt away
烟消云散
And there's a hero comes along
于是一位英雄翩翩而至
With the strengh to carry on
充满力量继续前行
And you cast your fears aside
你将恐惧置之脑后
And you know you can survive
你知道自己将屹立不倒
So when you feel like hope is gone
所以当你万念俱灰时
Look inside you will be strong
正视自己 坚强不屈
And you'll finally see the truth
你将最终大彻大悟
That a hero lies in you
英雄就在你心中
It's a long road
漫漫长路
When you face the world alone
当你独自面对这个世界
No one reaches out a hand for you to hold
无人向你伸出援助之手
You can find love
你寻觅到真爱
If you search within yourself
如果你探寻自己的内心世界
And the emptiness you felt
所有的空虚
Will disappear
烟消云散
And there's a hero comes along
于是一位英雄翩翩而至
With the strengh to carry on
充满力量继续前行
And you cast your fears aside
你将恐惧置之脑后
And you know you can survive
你知道自己将屹立不倒
So when you feel like hope is gone
所以当你万念俱灰时
Look inside you will be strong
正视自己 坚强不屈
And you'll finally see the truth
你将最终大彻大悟
That a hero lies in you
英雄就在你心中
Lord knows
上天知道
Dreams are hard to follow
梦想难以追随
But don't let anyone
但是不要让任何人
Tear them away, hey yeah
将梦想打碎  嘿 耶
Just hold on
坚韧不拔
There will be tomorrow
明天就会到来
In time You'll find the way
前途一片光明
And there's a hero comes along
于是一位英雄翩翩而至
With the strengh to carry on
充满力量继续前行
And you cast your fears aside
你将恐惧置之脑后
And you know you can survive
你知道自己将屹立不倒
So when you feel like hope is gone
所以当你万念俱灰时
Look inside you will be strong
正视自己 坚强不屈
And you'll finally see the truth
你将最终大彻大悟
That a hero lies in you
英雄就在你心中
压制:随Feng